A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Rockefeller Family, 1982-1986; 26; 57.72 Cubic Feet 140 letter document boxes, 8 legal document boxes, 1 wide letter document box, and 1 oversize box
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 7
      - Awards - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 683, Folder 1)
      - Biography (Box 683, Folder 2)
      - Biography - Book (Box 683, Folder 3)
      - Book Purchases and Donations (Box 683, Folder 4)
      - Clippings (Box 683, Folder 5)
      - Diary, 1985-1986 (Box 685, Folder 1-2)
      - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 685, Folder 3-4)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - A Christian Ministry in National Parks (Box 685, Folder 5, Box 686, Folder 1)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - Chasin, Laura (Box 686, Folder 2-3)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - Council of State Governments (Box 686, Folder 4)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center re: Sinatra and Pavarotti, 1982 (Box 687, Folder 1)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - Princeton University (Box 687, Folder 2-3)
      - 50th Wedding Anniversary, Jackson Hole, WY, 1984 August (Box 684, Folder 1-4)
      - 50th and 60th Wedding Anniversaries, 1984; 1994 (Box 684, Folder 5)
      - Finances (Box 692, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Open 2029.
      - Furnishings (Box 687, Folder 4)
      - Gifts - A-Z (Box 692, Folder 2-3)
      - Giving Program (Box 687, Folder 5)
      - Giving Program 1982 - A-Z (Box 688, Folder 1-2)
      - Giving Program 1983 - A-Z (Box 688, Folder 3-4, Box 689, Folder 1-2)
      - Giving Program 1984 - A-Z (Box 689, Folder 3-4)
      - Giving Program 1985 - A-Z (Box 690, Folder 1-2)
      - Giving Program 1986 - A-Z (Box 690, Folder 3, Box 691, Folder 1)
      - Investments - General (Box 691, Folder 2-3)
      - Investments - A-H (Box 691, Folder 4)
      - Investments - I-Z (Box 693, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Avtek Corp. (Box 693, Folder 2-4, Box 694, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Grosvenor Publications, Inc., 1982 (Box 694, Folder 2-5, Box 695, Folder 1-4, Box 696, Folder 1)
        Including but not limited to: Portfolio Magazine.
      - Investments - Resorts and Farm Investments (Summaries) (Box 696, Folder 2)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-Z (Box 696, Folder 3-4)
      - Jewelry (Box 696, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln School, 1982 (Box 696, Folder 6, Box 697, Folder 1)
      - Loans (Box 697, Folder 2)
      - Loans - Alice in Wonderland (Box 697, Folder 3)
      - Loans - Alice in Wonderland - Clippings (Box 697, Folder 4)
      - Loans - Alice in Wonderland - Printed Matter (Box 698, Folder 1-2)
      - Mail (Box 698, Folder 3-5)
      - Personal (Box 699, Folder 1-2)
      - Photos (Box 699, Folder 3)
      - Politics (Box 699, Folder 4)
      - Property (Box 699, Folder 5)
      - Property - Hawaii, Maui (Box 699, Folder 6)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue (Box 700, Folder 1)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - A-Z (Box 700, Folder 2-4)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Board of Directors - A-Z (Box 701, Folder 1)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Minutes-Meetings (Box 701, Folder 2)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - De Lorean, John Z. (Box 701, Folder 3)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 701, Folder 4, Box 702, Folder 1)
      - Property - New York City - 140 East 56th Street (Box 701, Folder 5)
      - Property - New York City - 340 East 64th Street (Box 702, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - General (Box 703, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - A-Z (Box 703, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - JY Ranch, 1981-1986 (Box 703, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch, 1983-1986 (Box 703, Folder 5)
      - Property - JY Ranch, 1984 (Box 704, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Appraisals (Box 704, Folder 2-3, Box 705, Folder 1-3)
        Restricted - Open 2029
      - Property - JY Ranch - Budget-Finances (Box 692, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Easements (Box 706, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Employees-Personnel-Staff - General (Box 705, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Employees-Personnel-Staff - A-Z (Box 705, Folder 5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Legal (Box 692, Folder 5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Long, Richard and Jane (Box 706, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Maps (Box 708, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Turner, Dennis and Shirlene (Box 706, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service, 1977-1986 (Box 706, Folder 4, Box 707, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Sale, 1977-1985 (Box 707, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Sale - Princeton, Dartmouth, MIT, Vermont Law School, Woodstock Foundation, and Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977-1985 (Box 708, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1982-1983 (Box 708, Folder 3-5)
        Includes appreciation correspondence.
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1984-1986 (Box 709, Folder 1-4)
        Includes appreciation correspondence
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 709, Folder 5)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kent House (Box 710, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Land Use Study, 1980-1981 (Box 710, Folder 2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Rockwood Hall - Appraisals (Box 710, Folder 3-4, Box 711, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Rockwood Hall - Sasaki Associates, Inc., 1978-1985 (Box 711, Folder 2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Rockwood Hall - IBM, 1977-1985 (Box 711, Folder 3)
      - Property - Tarrytown (Box 712, Folder 1)
      - Property - Tarrytown - Marymount Property, 1984-1986 (Box 712, Folder 2)
      - Property - Tarrytown - Marymount School, 1982-1983 (Box 712, Folder 3)
      - Property - Tarrytown - Marymount School - Clippings (Box 702, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock (Box 702, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Background Material (Box 702, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - A-L (Box 713, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Woodstock - M-Z (Box 714, Folder 1-5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Agendas (Box 715, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Articles (Box 715, Folder 5-6, Box 716, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Bailey House (Box 716, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings, Richard S. (Box 716, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Clippings (Box 716, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Debevoise, Thomas M. (Box 716, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Echo Acre (Cale House) (Box 717, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Employees (Box 721, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Endowment (Box 717, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Finances (Box 717, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Finances - Budget (Box 717, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Forestry Program (Box 718, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Hudson and Pacific Alliance (Box 718, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Harvey House (Box 718, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Humelsine, Carlisle H. (Box 718, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Lynch, Bryan J. (Box 718, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 718, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion - Lighting (Box 719, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Maps and Property Book (Box 719, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Martin House (Box 719, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Memos (Box 719, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Richardson House (Box 719, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock - Ross House (Box 720, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Sasaki & Associates (Box 720, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Taxes (Box 721, Folder 2)
        Restricted - Confidential material
      - Property - Woodstock - Winks, Robin W. (Box 720, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Town of Woodstock (Box 720, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm (Box 720, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm - Finances (Box 722, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Dairy (Box 722, Folder 2-4, Box 723, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Dairy - Finances (Box 723, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - A-Z (Box 723, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum (Box 724, Folder 1-2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - A-F (Box 724, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - G-Z (Box 725, Folder 1-2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Admissions (Box 725, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Agenda (Box 725, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Appreciation (Box 725, Folder 5)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Articles (Box 725, Folder 6)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Attendance (Box 726, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Biltmore Estate, Asheville, NC (Box 726, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Blueprints (Box 726, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Camp, Phillip Cabot (Box 726, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Dedication (Box 726, Folder 5)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Design and Production, 1982-1985 (Box 727, Folder 1-3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Design and Production - Final Treatment Outline (Box 728, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Employees (Box 721, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Employees - Brown, William G. (Box 721, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Employees - David, A. Donath (Box 721, Folder 5)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Finance - Budget (Box 728, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Hastings, Scott E. Jr., 1982-1984 (Box 728, Folder 3-4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Maine State Museum, 1981 (Box 729, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Monthly Report (Box 729, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Photos (Box 729, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Preview (Box 729, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Shelburne Museum, Inc., Shelburne, VT (Box 729, Folder 5)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Thresher Mill (Box 729, Folder 6)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 729, Folder 7)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 729, Folder 8)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation (Box 730, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 730, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Jennison, Peter S. (Box 730, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Jennison, Peter S. - Not an Ordinary Town: Woodstock the Second Hundred Years (Box 730, Folder 4, Box 731, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Legal (Box 738, Folder 5)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes-Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 731, Folder 2-4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes-Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 732, Folder 1-4, Box 733, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 733, Folder 2-4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Employees (Box 733, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Expansion (Box 733, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 734, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Memos (Box 735, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Printed Matter (Box 735, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - The Woodstock Resort Corporation-Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club Association, Inc. Proposed Merger (Box 735, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Sports Center (Box 735, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Chester B. Williamson Jr. (Box 735, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation (Box 735, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 736, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Jackson Hole (Box 737, Folder 1)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1977-1986 (Box 737, Folder 2)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - A-Z (Box 737, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Furnishings - A-Z (Box 738, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Photos (Box 738, Folder 3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Guest House (Box 738, Folder 4)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Master Plan (Box 739, Folder 1)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits (Box 739, Folder 2)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1982 June-1983 April (Box 739, Folder 3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Bid Documents Contracts and Budgets, 1981 (Box 739, Folder 4)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1981 May-October (Box 739, Folder 5)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1981 September-1982 May (Box 740, Folder 1)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch, 1980 November-1981 April (Box 740, Folder 2)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Change Orders, 1981-1982 (Box 740, Folder 3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Furnishings, 1981-1982 (Box 740, Folder 4)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Landscaping, 1981-1983 (Box 741, Folder 1)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Swimming Pool, 1981-1982 (Box 741, Folder 2)
      - Purchases - A-Z (Box 742, Folder 1-3, Box 743, Folder 1-4)
      - Schedules (Box 744, Folder 1)
      - Squaw Valley (Box 744, Folder 2)
      - Special Account "G", 1979-1985 (Box 745, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Confidential
      - Subscriptions (Box 744, Folder 3)
      - Taxes (Box 745, Folder 2)
      - Trips (Box 744, Folder 4)
      - Trips - Argentina, 1982 November (Box 744, Folder 5)
      - Trips - China, Japan and Hong Kong, 1985 (Box 746, Folder 1-2)
      - Trips - Europe, 1980 (Box 746, Folder 3)
      - Trips - Europe, 1982-1986 (Box 747, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Mexico (Box 747, Folder 2)
      - Trusts (Box 745, Folder 3)
      - Wallace Funds (Box 747, Folder 3-5)
      - Wallace Funds - A-Z (Box 748, Folder 1-3)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings (Box 748, Folder 4)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1986 April (Box 748, Folder 5, Box 749, Folder 1)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1986 July (Box 749, Folder 2-3)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1986 November 4 (Box 750, Folder 1)
      - Will, 1979-1985 (Box 745, Folder 4)
      - Works of Art - A-F (Box 750, Folder 2)
      - Works of Art - G-L (Box 750, Folder 3)
      - Works of Art - M-Q (Box 750, Folder 4)
      - Works of Art - R-S (Box 751, Folder 1)
      - Works of Art - T-Z (Box 751, Folder 2)
      - Works of Art - American Indian Collection (Box 751, Folder 3-4)
      - Works of Art - Dallin, Cyrys E. (Box 751, Folder 5)
      - Works of Art - Grandma Moses (Box 751, Folder 6)
      - Works of Art - Porcelains (Box 752, Folder 1)
      - Works of Art - Sotheby Parke Bernet (Box 752, Folder 2)
      - Yin-Yang (Box 752, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - A-Z (Box 752, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Addresses (Box 752, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Awards (Box 752, Folder 6, Box 753, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Awards - USO of Metropolitan New York (Box 753, Folder 2-3)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) (Box 680, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Beverkill Project (Box 680, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Beverkill Project - Beaverkill Falls Homeowners Association, Inc. (Box 680, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Wedding (Box 684, Folder 1)
      - Carmichael, Deborah (Box 629, Folder 2)
      - Case, Matthew (Box 629, Folder 3)
      - Case, Peter Rockefeller (Box 629, Folder 4)
      - Chasin, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Laura S. Rockefeller) (Box 629, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Wyatt Gordon (Box 764, Folder 8)
      - Waletzky, Dr. and Mrs. Jeremy P. and Lucy Rockefeller Hamlin, 1982-1985 (Box 771, Folder 4)
      - Waletzky, Dr. and Mrs. Jeremy P. and Lucy Rockefeller Hamlin - Charitable Lead Trust (Box 771, Folder 5)
      - Weber, Mr. and Mrs. Warren T. and Marion French Rockefeller, 1982-1986 (Box 771, Folder 6)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (and family), 8
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-Z (Box 753, Folder 4)
      - Estate, 1979-1980 (Box 741, Folder 3, Box 754, Folder 1-3, Box 755, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate, 1980-1982 (Box 755, Folder 3)
      - Estate, 1980-1984 (Box 755, Folder 4)
      - Estate - A-Z (Box 756, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate - Minutes-Meetings (Box 756, Folder 3)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro (Box 756, Folder 4)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro, 1979 (Box 757, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro, 1980 (Box 757, Folder 3)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro, 1981 (Box 757, Folder 4)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro, 1982-1986 (Box 758, Folder 1)
      - Estate - Porcelains (Box 758, Folder 2)
      - Estate - Sotheby Parke Bernet, Inc. (Box 758, Folder 3-4)
      - Friele, Berent (Box 759, Folder 1)
      - Memorials (Box 759, Folder 2)
      - Memorials - William A. Burden (Box 759, Folder 3)
      - Property - Monte Sacro, 1978 (Box 759, Folder 4)
      - Property - Seal Harbor, 1977 (Box 759, Folder 5)
      - Nelson Rockefeller Collection (Box 760, Folder 1-2)
        Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection, Inc. - Art collection
      - Nelson Rockefeller Publications, 1978 (Box 760, Folder 3)
      - Works of Art - Mexican Art Collection (Box 760, Folder 4)
      - Trust for Children - Texas Trust (Campo Alegre), 1979-1986 (Box 761, Folder 1)
      - Will (Box 761, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - A-F (Box 760, Folder 5-6)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - G-Z (Box 762, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Addresses-Remarks (Box 762, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Articles (Box 762, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Autographs (Box 762, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Awards (Box 762, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions (Box 763, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Photos, 1977-1984 (Box 763, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Property (Box 761, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Trips (Box 763, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy) - Works of Art (Box 763, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson Jr. (Box 761, Folder 4)
      - Buden, Mr. and Mrs. James P. and Clare M. Pierson (Box 628, Folder 5)
      - Buden, Mr. and Mrs. James P. and Clare M. Pierson - Giving Program, 1981-1985 (Box 629, Folder 1)
      - Lyden, John Pierpont and Carol (Box 632, Folder 7)
      - Menotti, Francis and Melinda Fitler (Box 632, Folder 8)
      - Morgan, Thomas B. and Mary (Box 634, Folder 1)
      - Morgan, Thomas B. and Mary - Giving Program (Box 634, Folder 2)
      - Morgan, Thomas B. and Mary - Giving Program, 1979-1983 (Box 634, Folder 3-4)
      - Morgan, Thomas B. and Mary - Giving Program, 1984-1986 (Box 635, Folder 1)
      - Murphy, James B. II (Box 635, Folder 2)
      - Pierson, Joseph (Box 636, Folder 3)
      - Pierson, Mary Louise (Box 636, Folder 4)
      - Pierson, Rachel (Box 636, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Ann R. (Box 636, Folder 6)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Giving Program (Box 636, Folder 7)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 636, Folder 8-10)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 637, Folder 1-2)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Payment Letters, 1981-1985 (Box 637, Folder 3-7)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Trusts (Box 637, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, Ann R. - Works of Art - Nelson A. Rockefeller Mexican Folk Art (Box 638, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, Doris S. (Box 673, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Igrid (Box 673, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Jennifer (Box 673, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Mark F. (Box 745, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Meile (Box 745, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Michael C. (Box 745, Folder 7)
        Restricted - Michael C. Rockefeller materials.
      - Rockefeller, Michael S. (Box 745, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller, Peter (Box 761, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Box 763, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Rodman C. - IBEC - Publications (Box 856)
      - Rockefeller, Rodman C. - Property (Box 764, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Barbara (Box 763, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Steven Clark, and Dori (Box 764, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Steven Clark, and Dori - Charitable Lead Trusts (Box 764, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Steven Clark Jr. (Box 764, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Stuart A. (Box 764, Folder 7)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller (and family), 9
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 765, Folder 1)
      - Winrock - David and Peggy Rockefeller Visit, 1986 April 16-17 (Box 765, Folder 2)
      - Estate - Winrock International (Box 765, Folder 3-4)
      - Estate - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development (Box 765, Folder 5)
      - Estate - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Merger (Box 763, Folder 8)
      - Estate - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation (Box 766, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul (Box 766, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1982-1986; 27; 3.22 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A (Box 769, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - B (Box 769, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - C (Box 769, Folder 6-7)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - D (Box 772, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - E (Box 772, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - F (Box 772, Folder 4-6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - G-U (Box 773, Folder 1-7)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - V-Z (Box 774, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 774, Folder 3)
      Includes the RBF Annual Report for 1978 and 1981, as well as the Planning Committee Report for 1983.
    - Annual Reports, 1986 (Box 774, Folder 4)
      Includes the RBF Annual Report for 1983, 1984, 1985 and 1986. The 1984 Annual Report also includes a reprint of the Francis Mading Deng essay "Crisis in African Development: A Social and Cultural Perspective".
    - Board of Trustees (Box 774, Folder 5)
    - Contributions (Box 774, Folder 6)
    - Deng, Dr. Francis (Box 774, Folder 7)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation (Box 774, Folder 8)
    - Finances (Box 775, Folder 1)
    - Grants (Box 775, Folder 2)
    - Mannes College of Music (Box 775, Folder 3)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1982 (Box 775, Folder 4-5, Box 776, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1983 (Box 776, Folder 3-4)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1984 (Box 777, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1985 (Box 777, Folder 3-4)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1986 (Box 777, Folder 5, Box 778, Folder 1)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 778, Folder 2)
    - Planning and Review Committee (Box 778, Folder 3)
    - Poland (Box 778, Folder 4)
    - Yankelovich, Skelly and White, Inc. (Box 778, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1982-1986; 28; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Family Fund - A-Z (Box 779, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report (Box 779, Folder 2)
      Includes: RFF Annual Reports, 1982-1986
    - Contributions (Box 781, Folder 1)